var opt = document.querySelector(".option_list");
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the Father of Computer?",
    answer: "Dr. Charles Babbage",
    options: [
      "Dr. Henry Williams",
      "Dr. Charles Babbage",
      "Dr. Sminton Hegons",
      "Dr. Martin D. Mello"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one is the True Avogadro Number?",
    answer: "6.02214076 × 10(23)",
    options: [
      "6.02214076 × 10(23)",
      "6.02356076 × 10(23)",
      "6.02674076 × 10(23)",
      "6.02964176 × 10(23)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who is Well known as Chhatrpati?",
    answer: "Maharaja Shivaji",
    options: [
      "Maharaja Sahu Raam",
      "Chakrvarti Chandragupt",
      "Maharaja Shivaji",
      "Maharana Pratap"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the Full Form Of NATO?",
    answer: "North Atlantic Treaty Organization",
    options: [
      "Northen America Trust Officials",
      "Not Act of Trust Office",
      "North Atlantic Treaty Organization",
      "Nation Acquire Trust Organization"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Full Form of PSLV is:",
    answer: "Polar Satellite Launch Vehicle",
    options: [
      "Particular Space Lattitude Vehicle",
      "Pressured Satellite Lengthy Vehicle",
      "Polar Satellite Launch Vehicle",
      "Pickup Space & Land Vector"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which Division of the Indian Para SF is known as 'Scorpion'?",
    answer: "10 Para SF",
    options: [
      "9 Para SF",
      "10 Para SF",
      "11 Para SF",
      "12 Para SF"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many Elements are there in periodic Table?",
    answer: "118",
    options: [
      "116",
      "117",
      "118",
      "120"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which one doesn't belong to Allies Powers (WW2):",
    answer: "Greenland",
    options: [
      "Greenland",
      "Great Britain",
      "The United States",
      "Soviet Union"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which Song has proclaimed as Suicidal song?",
    answer: "Gloomy Sunday",
    options: [
      "Gloomy Sunday",
      "Memories",
      "Bring me Home",
      "Give me some sunshine"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which one of the followings doesn't belong to Indian Air Force Fighter jet:",
    answer: "Boeing-AH 64",
    options: [
      "Mig-21",
      "Boeing-AH 64",
      "Mirage-2000",
      "Haltejas MK2"
    ]
  },
];